>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 当我们将某个值分配给变量时，或者
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: When we assign
some value to a variable, or
如果第 1 行已分配任何内容，那么该排序为缺省值，
in the case of line 1 having assigned
anything, that sort of defaults,
然后我们用一个像 typeof 一样的运算符来看待这个值
then we use an operator like typeof as our
first way of looking at that value and
确定它的身份，种类，种类。
determining something about its identity,
its kind, its type.
我们并不是问变量 v 的类型是什么
And we're not asking what's
the typeof the variable v,
我们问的是什么是当前在 v中的价值的类型。
we're asking what is the typeof
the value that is currently in v.
这就是第 2 行的内容
That's what line 2 says.
当前在 v中的值的类型是什么 ?
What is the typeof the value
that's currently in v?
您会注意到，在第 2 行中，它将返回未定义的字符串。
And you'll notice that on line 2
it returns the string undefined.
这很有趣，因为本质上我们可以想象
Now that's interesting because
essentially we can think of undefined
基本上是缺省值。
as basically a default value.
当空间的真空已经消除一切的时候，它是一个存在的价值。
It's a value that exists when the vacuum
of space has removed everything else.
当没有其他价值的时候
When there is no other value,
称为未定义值的值。
the value that you have is
called the undefined value.
记住这里有一个未定义的类型
And remember,
there's an undefined type with one and
其中只有一个值未定义。
only one value in it called undefined.
因此， typeof is telling is is undefined.
So typeof is telling us v
currently is undefined.
它已初始化并且未定义。
It got initialized and it's undefined.
顺便说下，这并不意味着它还没有价值。
And that, by the way,
does not mean it doesn't have a value yet.
很多人认为，未定义的手段还没有价值。
A lot of people think,
undefined means doesn't have a value yet.
最适合的思考方式是，当前没有值。
The most appropriate way to think about
it is, does not currently have a value.
因为这完全是可行的，而且往往会发生，
Because it's entirely plausible and
possible, and often happens,
您的变量或属性具有一些值，并且
that you have a variable or
a property that has some value and
然后再回到没有价值的状态。
then it goes back to the state
of not having a value anymore.
您将其设置为未定义，未定义它。
You set it to undefined, you undefine it.
这不会把它移除的
That doesn't remove it.
它不会删除它。
It doesn't delete it.
它并不神奇地让它消失。
It doesn't magically make it go away.
它只是把它带回那个状态，那里的值是没有定义的。
It just takes it back to that state where
the value that it's holding is undefined.
现在，当我分配字符串并表示 typeof v时，我将获得报价字符串。
Now, when I assign the string and
say typeof v, I get quote string.
当我分配数字时，将获取报价编号。
When I assign a number,
I get quote number.
你会注意到
You'll notice that
来自 typeof 运算符的所有这些返回值都是字符串。
all of these return values from
the typeof operator are strings.
这很关键我们会知道为什么后来我们被胁迫
That's critical and we'll see why
later when we get into coercion, but
你知道这对你来说是很重要的
it's critical for you to understand
this is an operator that guarantees
它将始终返回一个字符串。
that it will always return a string.
它不仅会返回一个字符串
And not only will it
always return a string,
它本质上是一个简短的 eNom 列表。
it's essentially a short eNom list.
只有一小部分的字符串才能返回。
There's only a very small subset of
strings that it will ever return.
没有一个是空字符串。
And none of them are the empty string.
所有这些值都不是诸如 null 或未定义的字符串。
None of them are these values that
aren't strings like null or undefined.
我在博客上都看到了这个错误。
And I see this mistake
all the time in blogs.
人们会说平等的，平等的，平等的，
People will say typeof equal,
equal undefined,
没加引号完全没有意义
without any quotes and
that makes no sense whatsoever because
字面上的打字机不可能把它退回去
the typeof operator literally
cannot return that.
猜猜我是怎么知道的
Guess how I know.
我看了这个规格
I read the spec.
它不返回未定义的值，它总是返回字符串。
It does not return an undefined value,
it always returns a string.
如果这个字符串是一个可预测的列表，那么我们就减少了
And if the string is a predictable
known list, then we've reduced
可能从这个地方回来的混乱的整个表面
the whole surface area of confusion of
what could possibly come back from this.
我们可以更好地预测其结果。
We can predict its outcome much better.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 这很重要
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: That'll
be important later on.
所以 typeof is 返回表示， hey ，
So typeof is returning
strings that represent, hey,
关于你能期望能做什么的线索
here's some clue as to what you
can expect to be able to do with
此特定类型的特定类型的值。
values of this particular
kind of this particular type.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 从经济角度来说，这就是我们在代码中可以依赖的东西。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Ergonomically, that's
what we can then rely upon in our code.
我们有一些东西可以作为一个数字。
We have something that is
going to behave as a number.
我们有一些东西要做一个字符串。
We have something that is
going to behave as a string.
你注意到我们没有像我们一样的价值观
You notice we don't have all the values
like we don't have a typeof within
一个数组来给我们这个词
an array to give us the word array.
所以它只会把我们的对象还给我们
So it's just gonna give us
back object because remember,
数组是对象的子类型。
arrays are subtypes of object.
所以我们需要进一步区分我们是否需要进入这些亚种
So we're gonna need further distinguishing
if we need to get into those subtypes,
但在顶层我们可以根据这一切来区分
but at the top level we can distinguish
roughly based on all of these.
现在，我提到这个清单上的空值是特别的。
Now, I mentioned the null
being on that list as special.
你会注意到当我们说打字机等于空时我很抱歉
You'll notice that when we say
typeof v equals null, I'm sorry,
当我们说 v 等于 null 和 typeof v时，我们会返回报价对象。
when we say v equals null and
typeof v, we get back quote object.
现在，这是一个历史事实。
Now, this is a historical
fact of JavaScript.
事实上在目前存在的这个规范中，
As a matter of fact, in the current
spec that exists at this moment,
它还是有一个来自 ES1 的声明本质上是
it still has a statement that was
there from ES1 which essentially
向开发者表示，如果您想要取消设置常规值，
indicated to developers that if you
wanted to unset a regular value,
如数字，您将使用未定义的值。
like a number, you would use undefined.
但是，如果您想要取消设置对象引用，那么将使用空值。
But if you wanted to unset an object
reference, you would use null.
我认为这也是为什么 typeof null 返回对象的历史原因的一部分。
And I think that's part of the historical
reason for why typeof null returns object.
但是这件事的真实真相我在推特上说了这么多年
But the real truth of the matter,
I was tweeting about this years back,
真正的真相是它只是一只虫子
and the real truth of the matter
is that it's just a bug.
应该已返回空值以告诉我们此值为
It ought to have returned quote null
to tell us that this a value of
类型为 NULL。
the type null.
遗憾的是，它返回引号对象，因此您必须更小心一点。
Unfortunately, it returns quote object, so
you have to be a little bit more careful.
你得确保当你做检查的时候
You have to make sure,
when you're doing a typeof check and
它会返回对象，确保它不是意外的是空的，
it returns object, make sure that
it's not accidentally the null,
因为这样你就不会得到目标但是值是空的
because then you're not gonna
get an object but a null value.
然后我们看到了这里的功能。
And then we see function here.
记住，功能不是正式类型
Remember, function is not an official type
最重要的是在最正式的意义上
at the top level,
in the most official sense.
但是，它在此处有自己的返回值，操作员的 typeof 运算符作为函数返回。
But it has its own return value here,
the typeof operator returns as function.
因此，它返回到我们的功能是有用的，但是数组不起作用。
So it's useful that it returns to us
function, but arrays, it doesn't.
数组仅返回对象。
Arrays just returns object.
很多这些都是关于 JavaScript的历史问题。
A lot of these are just, again,
historical things about JavaScript.
我们无法修复它们，因为如果我们修复它们，我们就会破坏一些代码。
We can't fix them because if we fix them,
we'd break a bunch of code.
所以不要抱怨和抱怨
So rather than whine or
complain about them,
我们应该好好学习他们的工作好吗
we should just learn them and
work around them, okay?
令人遗憾的是你不能只说打字机
It's regrettable that you
can't just say typeof, but
在语言方面还有其他的帮助，尤其是在排列方面，
there are other helpers in language,
in particular, with respect to array,
有 Array.isArray ，它会告诉你是否有一个阵列。
there's Array.isArray, and it'll tell you
for sure or not whether you have an array.
这就是我们如何区分这些原始值和它们的类型。
So that's how we distinguish these
primitive values with their types.
我们可以使用诸如 typeof 之类的实用程序，当我们需要更多细节时，
We can use utilities like typeof and
when we need a little bit more specifics,
我们可以使用诸如 Array.isArray之类的实用程序。
a little bit more nuance,
we can use utilities like Array.isArray.
他们会告诉我们什么是有价值的
They'll tell us something about the nature
of the value which tells us what
我们可以预料到的
we can expect.